last leg of conversation in Sanjeev man
3 from ICS he embodies executive
director the man way I look up to
because of the sheer discipline as far
as his his physical abilities are
concerned I you know one thing is to be
inspired but the other is to put that
inspiration into process and that's
where I like so this is so wonderful I
know that you were training very hard
for Tokyo the training itself is
wonderful but unfortunately sometimes
the light at the end of the tunnel is a
little dim and I leave you to tell the
story
talk about cancelled I guess yes sir
those of you I'm sorry to interrupt
engine for those of you who want to know
what we're talking about it's not just
physical fitness
he's a marathoner he run around the
Mumbai half marathon in his sub to our
timing and we're talking 150 people from
ICICI Lombard knocking - thank you so
much - Shakir for your kind words but
the fact of the matter is and I've
always told you on multiple occasions
that we enjoyed the journey man every
time he gets you know at the start line
of a marathon wherever we are running we
feel tremendously blessed that we could
make it it requires tremendous effort
not only from outside but the whole
family the ecosystem with support so
there are friends who come along and
kind of help us in this particular
journey we were aspiring this was my
sixth and the last of the world media
that I wanted to run and was very very
committed everything looked certain and
then I mean the wider the coronavirus
that each one of us is aware of has
happened there was a risk which was
there and we were all debating to go or
not to go but the Tokyo Marathon
authorities have made it easy for us
they've canceled the general category
only the elites can run which would be a
handful probably 225 of them will run
the marathon we had to reshuffle cancel
everything is still searching us - we if
we can go somewhere else but it's not
the same as being in Tokyo but that is
life you know we've enjoyed the journey
and maybe if you get lucky next year
there's always you know 2021 that is
available and as sportsmen and you know
we already you also have been a sports
man that you know the best thing about
being in this category you can lose but
you
be a loser you'll get up next day and
say okay let me try something else
we'll figure a way out tough luck and
it's not about only me there were quite
a few of us I think there are almost 50
60 people traveling from India to run
Tokyo my dad's marathon and each one of
them would have gone to much bigger
hardship that I have gone through but
that's life and you can only keep trying
that's what it says you're looking even
leaner than what you were last time
around so obviously there the drills are
the training for the Tokyo marathon even
though it got canceled was something
that you really push to the next level
well yes I think was trying like
everybody else we try to do our best
what's trying to stay away from injuries
because that's another challenge that I
have kept running into but all my fellow
runners you know one less thing right
now they know that there is a bit of a
pain that each of the runner goes
through and these activity requires a
fair amount of commitment physically and
more so mentally so we went through that
motion nothing big about it losing
weight I think where I stand a few cages
here and there can't make a lot of
difference in terms of running
injury-free so was trying to stay away
from some of these stuff which I really
enjoy eating but probably by will what
this weekend go and have a bit of that
also because we've got a break coming up
away and there's nothing much but the
good part is Rashid I'm sure you'll
understand this part that I really get
back to tennis
I had abstained maybe from junk food for
a while but besides that from tennis I
haven't played that for three months
which to me is in many ways my first
love so I look forward to hitting the
coats maybe tomorrow morning for change
and see how I feel having the racket
back in my hand and lovely and she was
saying on a lighter note that when the
Tokyo Marathon got canceled there was
actually a condolence meeting five leave
for it so five of her friends met up
over a coffee last evening and we really
really consoled each other saying that's
what life is all about but frankly
speaking
it was all for good fun types you know
you're looking for reasons to meet 150
people at the Mumbai marathon you
obviously inspiring people within the
confines of your office at least amazing
actually they don't require any
inspiration the office itself is full of
people who love to do that so they are
the ones who are inspiring me to run
with them and keep up with them and
every time I run the marathon a lot of
people come and say at your age if you
can run you're doing well and I say why
the hell you say that but really that's
the way it is wonderful talking to you
and I look forward to seeing you very
very soon best luck to you though I say
I say Lombard for the unicode campaign
and everybody is listening please go on
to all the official handles of I see SLO
mod across social media and LinkedIn and
vote really to make the helmet emoji
India's contribution to the world of
emojis and emoticons thank you thank you
so much